Guide to the North Carolina State University School of Design Historic Architecture Research Project Records, 1951-1976 UA 110.041
Special Collections Research Center
- UA 110.041 Series 4: Photographs, undated; 1 linear foot 3 archival card boxes
  The Historic Architecture Research Project Records photographs series includes approximately 2,000 black and white photographs of historic buildings across North Carolina, circa 1950s. Most photos are approximately 3"x 5"; some are 3"x 3" with some of the smaller photos mounted on index cards. Photos were originally stored in a card catalog, and all have a small hole punched in the middle near the bottom edge. They are organized alphabetically by county and accompanied by index cards listing name and location information. Most photo subjects are houses, though some other buildings (such as churches, schools, and offices) are represented.
  - Photographs of historic buildings in North Carolina counties Alamance - Forsyth, undated (Cardbox 26)
  - Photographs of historic buildings in North Carolina counties Franklin - Polk., undated (Cardbox 27)
  - Photographs of historic buildings in North Carolina counties Randolph - Yancey., undated (Cardbox 28)